{
    "id": "c269e8131efa4bb5b23f860730cb3340",
    "title": "Last and the last",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "dd123eb87f0a4e6b827840801524ac46",
            "title": "Last And The Last",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I had a discussion with him …………… week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last",
                        "the last"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I think ………………… time I met him was when I was in Singapore.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last",
                        "the last",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………….. met him in January.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last",
                        "the last",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had a cold ………………… week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last",
                        "the last",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Were you at the conference …………….. week?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last",
                        "the last",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We bought this house …………….. year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last",
                        "the last",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have lived here for …………….. year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last",
                        "the last",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have been too busy for ……………. three months.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last",
                        "the last",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is ……………… car I buy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "last",
                        "the last",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. few days have been very wet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Last",
                        "The last",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}